Guide to the Stewart M. Brandborg Papers 1932-2000
Maureen and Mike Mansfield Library, The University of Montana--Missoula
- The Wilderness Society, 1930-1977; Series IV; 28.0 linear ft.
  - Administration, 1954-1976; Subseries 1; 2.25 linear ft.
    - Staff Meeting Notes and Work Checklist, 1967-1968 (Box-folder 17/1)
    - Staff Meetings, 1965-1970 (Box-folder 17/2)
    - Staff Meetings, Minutes File, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 17/3)
    - Staff Meetings, Minutes File, 1973 (Box-folder 17/4)
    - Staff Organizational Chart, 1976 (Box-folder 17/5)
    - Staff Organizational Planning, 1960-1967 (Box-folder 17/6)
    - Staff Organizational Plans and Memos, 1968-1973 (Box-folder 17/7)
    - Staff Recruitment, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 17/8)
    - Staff Recruitment, 1975 (Box-folder 17/9)
    - Staff Review, Stewart M. Brandborg and Peeps Carney, undated (Box-folder 17/10)
    - Staffing, **RESTRICTED**, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 91/1)
    - Travel Expenses, 1960 (Box-folder 17/12)
    - Treasurer Report, John Krutilla, 1973 (Box-folder 17/13)
    - Treasury Reports, 1959-1968 (Box-folder 17/14)
    - Wilderness Review Division Job Descriptions, undated (Box-folder 17/15)
    - Wilderness Review Staffing and Duties, undated (Box-folder 17/16)
    - Wilderness Reviews Division, 1976 (Box-folder 18/1)
    - Wilderness Review-Staff Meetings/Process, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 18/2)
  - Subject Files, 1930-1977; Subseries 2; 25.75 linear ft.
    - A Way to the Wilderness Trip Program, 1968-1974 (Box-folder 18/3)
    - ABC Oil Spill News, undated (Box-folder 18/4)
    - Adirondacks Temporary Study Commission, 1969-1971 (Box-folder 18/5)
    - Advanced Wastewater Treatment Facility, 1973 (Box-folder 18/6)
    - Alaska, 1974-1976 (Box-folder 18/7)
    - Alaska, 80 Million Acres, 1973 (Box-folder 18/8-9)
    - Alaska, 80 Million Acres Advertisements, 1973 (Box-folder 18/10)
    - Alaska, 80 Million Acres, Stewart M. Brandborg Notes, 1973 (Box-folder 18/11)
    - Alaska, 80 Million Acres, Media Summary Notes, 1973 (Box-folder 18/12)
    - Alaska, Advertisements, 1973 (Box-folder 19/1)
    - Alaska, Articles and Alternatives, 1966-1972 (Box-folder 19/2)
    - Alaska Bill Amendments, 1972 (Box-folder 19/3)
    - Alaska Coalition, 1971-1973 (Box-folder 19/4)
    - Alaska Coalition, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 19/5-6)
    - Alaska Coalition, Letter to the President, 1971 (Box-folder 19/7)
    - Alaska Conservation Conference, 1969-1971 (Box-folder 19/8)
    - Alaska Conservation Society, 1969-1975 (Box-folder 19/9-10)
    - Alaska, D-2 Lands, 1972-1975 (Box-folder 19/11)
    - Alaska Federal-State Land-Use Planning Commission, 1975 (Box-folder 19/12)
    - Alaska Federation of Natives and Native Claims, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 19/13)
    - Alaska Field Report, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 19/14)
    - Alaska Geological Data, Valdez to Fairbanks, 1969 (Box-folder 19/15)
    - Alaska, Local Elections, 1974 (Box-folder 19/16)
    - Alaska, Mailer to Citizens, 1971 (Box-folder 19/17)
    - Alaska Map, Bureau of Land Management, 1972 (Box-folder 20/1)
    - Alaska, Media and Plans, 1973 (Box-folder 20/2)
    - Alaska National Interest Legislation, 1971 (Box-folder 20/3)
    - Alaska Native Claims Settlement Act, 1970-1973 (Box-folder 20/4)
    - Alaska Native Claims Settlement Act Sponsors, 1971 (Box-folder 20/5)
    - Alaska Native Claims Settlement and Related Bills, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 20/6-7)
    - Alaska Notes, Stewart M. Brandborg, 1971 (Box-folder 20/8-9)
    - Alaska Oil Plans, 1966-1969 (Box-folder 21/1)
    - Alaska Pipeline Amendment, 1973 (Box-folder 21/2)
    - Alaska Pipeline Amendments, 1973 (Box-folder 21/3)
    - Alaska Pipeline Background and Plans, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 21/4)
    - Alaska Pipeline Bill, Senate and House Debates, 1973 (Box-folder 21/5-7)
    - Alaska Pipeline Bills and Congressional Documents, 1973 (Box-folder 22/1)
    - Alaska Pipeline Brandborg Notes on Wilderness Society Activities, 1970-1972 (Box-folder 22/2)
    - Alaska Pipeline Citizen Flyers, 1973 (Box-folder 22/3)
    - Alaska Pipeline Clippings, 1971-1973 (Box-folder 22/4)
    - Alaska Pipeline Clippings, 1973 (Box-folder 22/5)
    - Alaska Pipeline Committee Reports, 1973 (Box-folder 22/6)
    - Alaska Pipeline, Congressman Morris Udall, 1971-1973 (Box-folder 22/7)
    - Alaska Pipeline Environmental Impact Statement Draft, 1971 (Box-folder 22/8)
    - Alaska Pipeline February-March, 1973 (Box-folder 22/9)
    - Alaska Pipeline Final Environmental Impact Statement, 1972 (Box-folder 22/10)
    - Alaska Pipeline House and Senate Testimony, 1973 (Box-folder 23/1)
    - Alaska Pipeline House and Senate Testimony, 1973 (Box-folder 23/2-3)
    - Alaska Pipeline Information and Notes, 1973 (Box-folder 23/4)
    - Alaska Pipeline Internal Memos, 1973 (Box-folder 23/7)
    - Alaska Pipeline Land Use Planning Commission, 1973-1975 (Box-folder 23/5)
    - Alaska Pipeline Letters of Support, 1972 (Box-folder 23/6)
    - Alaska Pipeline Notes and Memos, 1975 (Box-folder 23/8)
    - Alaska Pipeline Planning, 1973 (Box-folder 24/1)
    - Alaska Pipeline Press Conference, Department of the Interior, 1972 (Box-folder 24/2)
    - Alaska Pipeline Public Correspondence, 1971-1973 (Box-folder 24/3)
    - Alaska Pipeline Public Hearings and Draft Statement, 1971-1973 (Box-folder 24/4-5)
    - Alaska Pipeline Route Notes, 1973 (Box-folder 24/6)
    - Alaska Pipeline Senate Bill 1081, 1973 (Box-folder 24/7)
    - Alaska Pipeline Special Appeal, Negative Letters, 1972 (Box-folder 24/8)
    - Alaska Pipeline Split Decisions, 1971 (Box-folder 24/9)
    - Alaska Pipeline Testimony, 1973 (Box-folder 24/10)
    - Alaska Planning Dinner, 1972 (Box-folder 24/11)
    - Alaska Press Releases, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 24/12)
    - Alaska Public Interest Coalition, 1973 (Box-folder 24/13)
    - Alaska Public Interest Coalition and Alaska Action Committee, 1973 (Box-folder 24/14)
    - Alaska Railroads and Highways through Public Lands, 1970 (Box-folder 24/15)
    - Alaska Related Congressional Records, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 24/16)
    - Alaska Related Introduced Bills, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 24/17)
    - Alaska Representative Jim Kowalsky, 1973 (Box-folder 24/18)
    - Alaska Task Force, Oil, Gas, and Roads, 1974 (Box-folder 24/19)
    - Alaska, Withdrawals, 1972 (Box-folder 24/20)
    - Alaska, Work Plans, 1975 (Box-folder 25/1)
    - Alaska-Canada Planning, 1973-1975 (Box-folder 25/2)
    - Aldo Leopold Foundation, undated (Box-folder 25/3)
    - Alternative Oil Delivery Systems, undated (Box-folder 25/4)
    - Amax Mining in Wyoming, 1974 (Box-folder 25/5)
    - American Association for the Advancement of Science, Meeting Minutes, 1968 (Box-folder 25/6)
    - American Association for the Advancement of Science, Section X, 1975 (Box-folder 25/7)
    - American Bar Association, 1973 (Box-folder 25/8)
    - American Committee for International Conservation, 1975 (Box-folder 25/9)
    - American Motors Conservation Award, Clifton R. Merritt, 1974 (Box-folder 25/10)
    - Analysis of a Political Interest Group: The Wilderness Society, 1968 (Box-folder 25/14)
    - Clifton P. Anderson, 1972 (Box-folder 25/11)
    - Apostle Islands National Lakeshore, 1966-1970 (Box-folder 25/14)
    - Appalachian Greenway, 1975 (Box-folder 25/15)
    - Appalachian Highlands Association, 1970 (Box-folder 25/16)
    - Arctic Slope Regional Corporation, 1972 (Box-folder 25/17)
    - Areas of Agreement Committee, 1975 (Box-folder 25/18)
    - Arizona Wilderness Association Proposals, 1969 (Box-folder 25/19)
    - Arizona Wilderness Workshop, 1968 (Box-folder 25/20)
    - Arizonans for Water Without Waste, 1969 (Box-folder 25/21)
    - Assateague Island National Seashore, 1965-1967 (Box-folder 25/22)
    - Assistant Secretary for Fish, Wildlife, and Parks, Nat Reed, 1973-1975 (Box-folder 25/23)
    - Association of Data Processing Service Organizations, Incorporated, Supreme Court Decision, 1970 (Box-folder 25/24)
    - Atlantic Richfield Company, 1973 (Box-folder 25/25)
    - The "B", 1967-1975 (Box-folder 25/27)
    - Frank Barry, Plans, 1975 (Box-folder 25/28)
    - Frank Barry, Work Plans, 1970-1974 (Box-folder 25/29)
    - Basic Brandborg, A Pattern for Speeches on Wilderness Conservation, 1966 (Box-folder 25/30)
    - Leslie F. Beaty Thesis: Attitudes of Federal Natural Resource Decision Makers Toward Citizen Participation, 1964 (Box-folder 25/31)
    - Benton MacKaye Memorial, 1975 (Box-folder 25/32)
    - Bernard Frank for Action, 1964 (Box-folder 25/33)
    - Bernie Frank Dedication, 1975 (Box-folder 25/34)
    - Bills Regarding the National Wilderness Preservation System, Correspondence, 1967-1971 (Box-folder 25/35)
    - Bills Regarding the National Wilderness Preservation System, Correspondence, 1967-1971 (Box-folder 26/1)
    - Bi-Regional Conferences, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 26/2)
    - Bitterroot National Forest, 1975 (Box-folder 26/3)
    - Bitterroot National Forest Multiple Use Plan, 1972 (Box-folder 26/4)
    - Bitterroot Timber Controversy, 1969-1992 (Box-folder 26/5-8)
    - Bitterroot Timber Controversy, 1969-1992 (Box-folder 27/1)
    - Black Mountain Road, Idaho, 1967 (Box-folder 27/2)
    - Blue Plains Sewage Treatment Plant, 1975 (Box-folder 27/3)
    - Board of Church and Society Project, Methodist Church, 1973 (Box-folder 27/4)
    - Board of Regents Cooperation, 1975 (Box-folder 27/5)
    - Boston Television Series on National Parks, undated (Box-folder 27/6)
    - Boundary Waters Canoe Area, 1973 (Box-folder 27/7)
    - Guy M. Brandborg Correspondence, 1971-1973 (Box-folder 27/8)
    - Guy M. Brandborg Correspondence, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 27/9)
    - British Columbia Environmental Council, 1971 (Box-folder 27/10)
    - Brotherhood of Venery, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 27/11)
    - Bureau of Land Management, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 27/12)
    - Bureau of Land Management Organic Act, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 27/13)
    - Bureau of Land Management Organic Act, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 27/14)
    - Dale Burk, 1971-1975 (Box-folder 27/15)
    - Dale A. Burk, Journalist, Bitterroot Controversy, Correspondence, 1975 (Box-folder 27/16)
    - Earl L. Butz, 1973 (Box-folder 27/17)
    - Bob Cahn, 1972 (Box-folder 27/18)
    - Canada-United States Environmental Council, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 27/19-20)
    - Canada-United States Environmental Council Meeting Notes, 1975 (Box-folder 27/21)
    - Canadian Notes, undated (Box-folder 28/1)
    - Canadian Wilderness Associations, 1964-1969 (Box-folder 28/2)
    - Canadian Wilderness Associations, Publications, 1969-1973 (Box-folder 28/3)
    - Canyonlands National Recreation Area, 1962-1970 (Box-folder 28/3)
    - Carbon copies of Correspondence, 1974 (Box-folder 28/4)
    - Virginia "Peeps" Carney, 1968-1974 (Box-folder 28/5)
    - Carrying Capacity of Wilderness Areas, 1963 (Box-folder 28/6)
    - Cash Farm Lease, 1969 (Box-folder 28/7)
    - Chaco Canyon National Monument, New Mexico, 1968-1969 (Box-folder 28/8)
    - Chicago Mountaineering Club, 1968 (Box-folder 28/9)
    - Chichagof-Yakobi Wilderness Area, 1968 (Box-folder 28/10)
    - Citizen Participation/Public Involvement Skills Workbook, 1975 (Box-folder 28/11-12)
    - Citizen's Committee on Natural Resources, 1969-1974 (Box-folder 28/13-14)
    - Citizens for Clean Water Package, 1972 (Box-folder 28/15)
    - Citizens for Moss Island at Little Falls, New York, 1975 (Box-folder 28/16)
    - Clippings, 1969-1972 (Box-folder 28/17)
    - Clippings, 1971-1973 (Box-folder 28/18)
    - Clippings, 1971-1978 (Box-folder 29/1)
    - Clippings, Gila Wilderness, Everglades National Park, Florida Barge Canal, 1969 (Box-folder 29/2)
    - Clippings: Personalities, 1955-1957 (Box-folder 29/3-4)
    - "Close Out", Interior Department, 1968 (Box-folder 29/5)
    - Coalition for National Population Policy, 1973 (Box-folder 29/6)
    - Colorado Magazine Research, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 29/7)
    - Colorado River, Correspondence and Clippings, 1964 (Box-folder 29/8)
    - Colorado Wilderness Plans, 1975 (Box-folder 29/9)
    - Comments on Proposed Regulations for Public Use, 1975 (Box-folder 29/10)
    - Community Leader Training, Handbook and Publications, 1968 (Box-folder 29/11)
    - Conference Participants Rosters, 1974-1976 (Box-folder 29/12)
    - Congressmen Aspinall, Colorado, 1972 (Box-folder 29/13)
    - Conservation Foundation, 1972-1975 (Box-folder 29/14-15)
    - Conservation Foundation, 1974 (Box-folder 29/16)
    - The Conservation Foundation, Correspondence, 1972 (Box-folder 30/1)
    - Conservation Foundation Newsletters, 1968-1972 (Box-folder 30/2)
    - Conservation Foundation, Public Affairs Committee, 1968 (Box-folder 30/3)
    - Conservation Foundation, Symposium on National Parks for the Future, 1972 (Box-folder 30/4)
    - Conservation Foundation, Woodstock Conference, 1972 (Box-folder 30/5)
    - Conservation Research Council, 1967-1971 (Box-folder 30/6)
    - Constituency Building and Public Involvement Articles, 1975-1982 (Box-folder 30/7-8)
    - Consultant Schedules, 1975 (Box-folder 30/9)
    - Toby Cooper, 1974 (Box-folder 30/10)
    - Cooperators for Wilderness, 1973-1975 (Box-folder 30/11)
    - Corporate Monitors, 1973 (Box-folder 30/12)
    - Correspondence Regarding Membership, 1973 (Box-folder 30/13)
    - Cosmos Club, 1974 (Box-folder 30/14)
    - Council on Environmental Quality, 1970 (Box-folder 30/15)
    - Council on Environmental Quality, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 30/16)
    - Coyote Ecology, 1972-1975 (Box-folder 30/17)
    - Crandall Plans Notes, 1970 (Box-folder 30/18)
    - Harry Crandell, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 30/19)
    - Cumberland Gap National Historical Park, 1967 (Box-folder 31/1)
    - Rupert Cutler, Assistant Executive Director, 1968 (Box-folder 31/2)
    - Rupert M. Cutler, Assistant Executive Director, Correspondence, 1969 (Box-folder 31/3)
    - Rupert M. Cutler, Assistant Executive Director, Correspondence, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 31/4)
    - D.O., 1975 (Box-folder 31/5)
    - Dams, Montana Wilderness, 1963 (Box-folder 31/6)
    - De Facto Wilderness Review, United States Forest Service, 1971 (Box-folder 31/7-8)
    - De Facto Wilderness Review, United States Forest Service, Sierra Club, undated (Box-folder 31/9)
    - De Facto Wilderness Studies in Southeastern Alaska, 1963-1965 (Box-folder 31/10)
    - Defenders of Wildlife, 1966-1974 (Box-folder 31/11)
    - Defenders of Wildlife, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 31/12-14)
    - Defenders of Wildlife, 1973 (Box-folder 31/15)
    - Defenders of Wildlife, Inactive, 1971-1973 (Box-folder 32/1-2)
    - Delmarva Peninsula, Atlantic Ocean, 1968-1969 (Box-folder 32/3)
    - Denver Wilderness Mailers, 1972 (Box-folder 32/4)
    - Denver-Consultant Planning, 1972 (Box-folder 32/5)
    - Department of the Interior, 1973-1975 (Box-folder 32/6)
    - Department of Interior Transition, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 32/7)
    - Desert Protective Council, Incorporated, 1967 (Box-folder 32/8)
    - Desolation Valley Wilderness Bill, 1969 (Box-folder 32/9)
    - Ernest Dickerman, 1975-1986 (Box-folder 32/10)
    - Durango, Colorado, Continental Divide Trail, 1967 (Box-folder 32/11)
    - Dutch Lunch Group, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 32/12)
    - Earthcare Wilderness Conference, 1975 (Box-folder 32/13)
    - Eastern Wilderness, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 32/14)
    - Eastern Wilderness Areas Act, 1975 (Box-folder 32/15)
    - Economic and Financial Concentration Resolution, 1971 (Box-folder 32/16)
    - Elk Preservation, 1975 (Box-folder 32/17)
    - Energy Crisis Articles, 1970-1977 (Box-folder 32/18)
    - Energy Crisis Congressional Remarks, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 32/19)
    - Energy Policy Project, "A time to choose", 1974 (Box-folder 32/20)
    - Environmental Defense Fund, 1975 (Box-folder 32/21)
    - Environmental Policy Center, 1973 (Box-folder 32/22)
    - Environmental Policy Center, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 32/23)
    - Environmental Policy Center, 1975 (Box-folder 32/24)
    - Environmental Programs for the Future, 1975 (Box-folder 32/25)
    - Environmental Protection Agency, 1975 (Box-folder 32/26)
    - Environmental Protection Agency Action, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 32/27)
    - Environmental Protection Agency Deputy Administrator John R. Quarles, 1974 (Box-folder 32/28)
    - Environmental Protection Agency, Ross Train, 1974 (Box-folder 32/29)
    - Environmental Quality Education Act and Clean Air Act, 1971 (Box-folder 33/1)
    - Equipment Manufacturers, 1975 (Box-folder 33/2)
    - Everglades National Park, 1955-1970 (Box-folder 33/3)
    - Gary Everhardt, National Park Service, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 33/4)
    - Executive Office of the President, Office of Science and Technology, 1968 (Box-folder 33/5)
    - Exploratory project for Economic Alternatives, 1976 (Box-folder 33/6)
    - Faces of Wilderness, 1973 (Box-folder 33/7)
    - Falls Creek Project, undated (Box-folder 33/8)
    - Federal Power Commission News, 1968 (Box-folder 33/9)
    - Federal Power Commission Proceedings, Joint Strategy, 1975 (Box-folder 33/10)
    - Fellows and Development Program Yearbooks, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 33/11)
    - Fred Ferber, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 33/12)
    - Fred Ferber, Sussex Woodlands, Inc., 1969-1973 (Box-folder 33/13)
    - Field Leadership Program, Book I, Salt Lake, Indianapolis, 1974 (Box-folder 33/14-17)
    - Field Leadership Program, Book II, St. Louis, Cedar City, Atlantic City, Pinkham Notch, 1974 (Box-folder 34/1-4)
    - Field Leadership Program, Book III, Chicago, Atlanta, Boise, Minneapolis, Chevy Chase, 1974 (Box-folder 34/5-8)
    - Fish and Wildlife Service Programs and Management Policies, 1975 (Box-folder 35/1)
    - Flathead River, North Fork Land Owner's Association, 1973 (Box-folder 35/2)
    - Florida Wilderness, 1968-1970 (Box-folder 35/3)
    - Follow-up issues, 1964 (Box-folder 35/4)
    - Ford Foundation Grants in Resources and Environment, 1968 (Box-folder 35/5)
    - Gerald Ford, 1974 (Box-folder 35/6)
    - Forest and Rangeland Renewable Resource Planning Act, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 35/7)
    - Forest Hearing, 1972-1976 (Box-folder 35/8-9)
    - Forest Service Cooperative Program, 1975 (Box-folder 35/10)
    - Forest Service Cooperative Project, 1975 (Box-folder 35/11)
    - Forest Service Hearings Testimony, 1973 (Box-folder 35/12)
    - Forest Service News, 1974 (Box-folder 35/13)
    - Forest Service Timber Decision, 1974 (Box-folder 35/14)
    - Forest Service Timber Management Plans for Colorado, 1975 (Box-folder 35/15)
    - Forest Service vs. Sierra Club, De Facto Suit, undated (Box-folder 35/16)
    - Forest Service, Program for the Future, 1973 (Box-folder 35/17)
    - Forest Timber Conservation and Management Act, 1970 (Box-folder 35/18)
    - Forestry Education Program Development, 1967-1969 (Box-folder 35/19)
    - Forestry Issue, Bitterroot National Forest, 1975 (Box-folder 35/20)
    - Forestry Issues, 1974-1977 (Box-folder 36/1-3)
    - Forestry Programs, Clearcutting on the Bitterroot National Forest, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 36/4-5)
    - Foundation, 1975 (Box-folder 36/6)
    - Bernie Frank Dedication, 1975 (Box-folder 36/7)
    - Friends of the Earth, 1973 (Box-folder 36/8)
    - Michael Frome, 1968-1973 (Box-folder 36/9)
    - Michael Frome, Book, 1975 (Box-folder 36/10)
    - Michael Frome, Book Promotion, 1974 (Box-folder 36/11)
    - Michael Frome, Issues, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 36/12)
    - Michael Frome, Writings, Correspondence, 1971-1975 (Box-folder 36/13)
    - Funding Projects, 1975 (Box-folder 36/14)
    - General Workshop Materials, 1967-1968 (Box-folder 36/15)
    - Publications, Ann Geracimos, 1974 (Box-folder 36/16)
    - Gila Wilderness Commemorative, 1954-1974 (Box-folder 36/17)
    - Glacier Peak Wilderness Area, 1957-1967 (Box-folder 36/18)
    - Good Life Project, 1974 (Box-folder 37/1)
    - Good Life Project, 1974 (Box-folder 37/2)
    - Grand Canyon Indian Lands, 1974 (Box-folder 37/3)
    - Grand Canyon National Park, 1968 (Box-folder 37/4)
    - Grand Canyon, Central Arizona Project, and Hooker Dam, 1967 (Box-folder 37/5-7)
    - Grant-in-Aid Correspondence, 1974 (Box-folder 37/8)
    - Great Smoky Mountains National Park, 1965-1970 (Box-folder 37/9-10)
    - Great Smoky Mountains National Park, 1966 (Box-folder 37/11)
    - Great Swamp Wilderness Area, 1967 (Box-folder 37/12)
    - Great Swamp Wilderness Proposal, 1968 (Box-folder 37/13)
    - Green America, 1975 (Box-folder 38/1)
    - Grizzly Bear Issues Notes and Drafts, 1975 (Box-folder 38/2)
    - John Hall, 1969 (Box-folder 38/3)
    - John Hall, Assistant Executive Director, Correspondence, 1969 (Box-folder 38/4)
    - Governor Jay Hammond, Alaska, 1975 (Box-folder 38/5)
    - Havasu and Superstition Management Plan, 1971 (Box-folder 38/6)
    - Helena National Forest, Lincoln-Scapegoat Backcountry, 1965-1969 (Box-folder 38/7-8)
    - Hells Canyon Preservation Council, Inc., 1969-1971 (Box-folder 38/9)
    - Ruth Higbie, 1975 (Box-folder 38/10)
    - High Rock Canyon-Black Rock Desert, 1975 (Box-folder 38/11)
    - High Uintas Wilderness, Ashley and Wasatch National Forests, Utah, 1968 (Box-folder 38/12)
    - Ed Hilliard, Vice President, Correspondence, 1969 (Box-folder 38/13)
    - Ed Hilliard, Vice President, Correspondence, 1969-1972 (Box-folder 38/14)
    - Hilltop Mining Bills, Correspondence, 1972 (Box-folder 38/15)
    - Discussion and Planning, Ed Hilliard, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 38/16)
    - Honoraria, Stewart Brandborg, 1969-1971 (Box-folder 38/17)
    - Hooker Dam Central Arizona Project, Correspondence, 1967-1968 (Box-folder 38/18)
    - Hooker Dam and Central Projects, 1961-1967 (Box-folder 38/19)
    - Hooker Dam Project, Bills, Letters to Congressmen, and Statements, 1967-1968 (Box-folder 39/1-3)
    - Hooker Dam, Central Arizona Project, 1968 (Box-folder 39/4)
    - Hooker Dam, Central Arizona Project, 1967-1968 (Box-folder 39/5)
    - Hooker Dam, Gila Wilderness, 1967-1970 (Box-folder 39/6-8)
    - House and Senate Interior Committee Assignments, 1973 (Box-folder 39/9)
    - House Proposal, 1973 (Box-folder 39/10)
    - House Subcommittee Testimony, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 39/11)
    - House Subcommittees on Public Lands, 1969-1973 (Box-folder 40/1)
    - Thatcher Hubbard, Northwest Steelheaders, Correspondence, 1970-1973 (Box-folder 40/2)
    - Hubert Humphrey, 1972 (Box-folder 40/3)
    - Idaho Wildlife Federation, 1973 (Box-folder 40/4)
    - Interior Department, Wilderness Act Regulations for Mining, 1967-1968 (Box-folder 40/5)
    - Interior Department-Strategies, Plans, 1975 (Box-folder 40/6)
    - Internal Revenue Service, Recent Conservation Proposition, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 40/7)
    - International Union for Conservation of Nature and Natural Resources, 1974 (Box-folder 40/8)
    - International Wilderness Brochure, 1974 (Box-folder 40/9)
    - Jack Beidler Memorial Fund, 1975 (Box-folder 40/10)
    - Joint Senate Interior and Commerce Committee Testimony, 1976 (Box-folder 40/11)
    - Kalamazoo Nature Center, 1970 (Box-folder 40/12)
    - Kansas Conference, 1975 (Box-folder 40/13)
    - Land and Water Conservation Fund Act, 1968 (Box-folder 40/14)
    - Land Policy Program for Pennsylvania and Lycoming County, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 40/15)
    - Leaders' Letter, 1975 (Box-folder 40/16)
    - Leadership Development Working Conference, 1969-1974 (Box-folder 40/17)
    - Leadership Workshop, 1956-1970 (Box-folder 40/18-19)
    - Legislative Activities, 1972 (Box-folder 41/1)
    - Letters for Checking and Reply, 1962-1964 (Box-folder 41/2)
    - Letters to Mail, 1974 (Box-folder 41/3)
    - Life Magazine, 1970 (Box-folder 41/4)
    - Lincoln-Scapegoat Wilderness and Representative, Arnold Olsen, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 41/5)
    - Lincoln-Scapegoat Wilderness Area, 1964-1970 (Box-folder 41/6)
    - Lincoln-Scapegoat Wilderness Area, 1969-1971 (Box-folder 41/7-8)
    - Litigation Coordination, Sierra Club and The Wilderness Society, 1975 (Box-folder 41/9)
    - Litigation Plans, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 41/10)